<theme>
   <variables>
      <systemName>Amiga 600</systemName>
      <systemDescription>The Amiga 600, also known as A600, is a home computer introduced in March 1992 by Commodore. It is the last Amiga model based on the Motorola 68000 and the 1990 ECS chipset. It is a redesigned version of the Amiga 500 Plus, adding the option for an internal hard drive and a PCMCIA slot. Lacking a numeric keypad, the A600 is only slightly larger than a standard PC keyboard, weighing approximately 2.72 kg. It came with AmigaOS 2.0, which was considered easier to use than previous versions of the operating system.</systemDescription>
      <systemManufacturer>Commodore</systemManufacturer>
      <systemReleaseYear>1985</systemReleaseYear>
      <systemReleaseDate>1985-07-23</systemReleaseDate>
      <systemReleaseDateFormated>March 1992</systemReleaseDateFormated>
      <systemHardwareType>Computer</systemHardwareType>
      <systemCoverSize>3-4</systemCoverSize>
      <systemColor>C171A5</systemColor>
      <systemColorPalette1>192753</systemColorPalette1>
      <systemColorPalette2>5BA079</systemColorPalette2>
      <systemColorPalette3>F9EA38</systemColorPalette3>
      <systemColorPalette4>ED2224</systemColorPalette4>
   </variables>
   <language name="es_ES">
      <variables>
         <systemDescription>El Amiga 600, también conocido como A600, es un ordenador doméstico introducido en marzo de 1992 por Commodore. Es el último modelo de Amiga basado en el Motorola 68000 y el conjunto de chips ECS de 1990. Es una versión rediseñada del Amiga 500 Plus, que añade la opción de un disco duro interno y un puerto PCMCIA. Al carecer de teclado numérico, el A600 es solo un poco más grande que un teclado de PC estándar, con un peso aproximado de 2,72 kg. Se entregaba con AmigaOS 2.0, considerado más fácil de usar que las versiones anteriores del sistema operativo.</systemDescription>
         <systemReleaseDateFormated>Marzo de 1992</systemReleaseDateFormated>
         <systemHardwareType>Computadora doméstica</systemHardwareType>
      </variables>
   </language>
</theme>