<theme>
   <variables>
      <systemName>Atari 5200</systemName>
      <systemDescription>The Atari 5200 SuperSystem, commonly known as the Atari 5200, is a second generation (1976–1992) video game console developed and distributed by Atari, Inc. It was released in November 1982 in North America at a retail price of $269. It was not released outside North America. The 5200's internal hardware was almost identical to Atari's 8-bit computers however it came with an innovative controller featuring a 360-degree non-centering joystick with a numeric keypad, start, pause, and reset buttons. The console was discontinued on May 21, 1984.</systemDescription>
      <systemManufacturer>Atari</systemManufacturer>
      <systemReleaseYear>1982</systemReleaseYear>
      <systemReleaseDate>1982-11-01</systemReleaseDate>
      <systemReleaseDateFormated>November 1, 1982</systemReleaseDateFormated>
      <systemHardwareType>Console</systemHardwareType>
      <systemCoverSize>3-4</systemCoverSize>
      <systemColor>3D5799</systemColor>
      <systemColorPalette1>1E6547</systemColorPalette1>
      <systemColorPalette2>CFA634</systemColorPalette2>
      <systemColorPalette3>973E3A</systemColorPalette3>
      <systemColorPalette4>1C6EB8</systemColorPalette4>
   </variables>
   <language name="es_ES">
      <variables>
         <systemDescription>El Atari 5200 SuperSystem, comúnmente conocido como el Atari 5200, es una consola de videojuegos de segunda generación (1976–1992) desarrollada y distribuida por Atari, Inc. Fue lanzada en noviembre de 1982 en América del Norte a un precio de venta de $269. No fue lanzada fuera de América del Norte. El hardware interno del 5200 era casi idéntico al de los ordenadores de 8 bits de Atari, sin embargo, venía con un control innovador que presentaba un joystick no centrado de 360 grados con un teclado numérico, botones de inicio, pausa y reinicio. La consola fue descontinuada el 21 de mayo de 1984.</systemDescription>
         <systemReleaseDateFormated>1 de noviembre de 1982</systemReleaseDateFormated>
         <systemHardwareType>Consola</systemHardwareType>
      </variables>
   </language>
</theme>