<theme>
   <variables>
      <systemName>Atari ST</systemName>
      <systemDescription>The Atari ST is a line of home computers from Atari Corporation and the successor to the Atari 8-bit family. The initial model, the 520ST, saw limited release in April–June 1985 and was widely available in July. The 520ST is the first personal computer to come with a bitmapped color GUI, using a version of Digital Research's GEM released in February 1985. The 1040ST, released in 1986, is the first personal computer to ship with a megabyte of RAM in the base configuration and also the first with a cost-per-kilobyte of less than US$1.

The Atari ST is part of a mid-1980s generation of home computers that have 16 or 32-bit processors, 256 KB or more of RAM, and mouse-controlled graphical user interfaces. This generation includes the Macintosh, Amiga, Apple IIGS, and in some markets the Acorn Archimedes. "ST" officially stands for "Sixteen/Thirty-two", which refers to the Motorola 68000's 16-bit external bus and 32-bit internals.

The ST was sold with either Atari's color monitor or the less expensive monochrome monitor. The system's color graphics modes are only available on the former while the highest-resolution mode needs the monochrome monitor.</systemDescription>
      <systemManufacturer>Atari</systemManufacturer>
      <systemReleaseYear>1985</systemReleaseYear>
      <systemReleaseDate>1985-06-01</systemReleaseDate>
      <systemReleaseDateFormated>June 1, 1985</systemReleaseDateFormated>
      <systemHardwareType>Computer</systemHardwareType>
      <systemCoverSize>3-4</systemCoverSize>
      <systemColor>0088D1</systemColor>
      <systemColorPalette1>172E7E</systemColorPalette1>
      <systemColorPalette2>3C62A7</systemColorPalette2>
      <systemColorPalette3>000000</systemColorPalette3>
      <systemColorPalette4>ECECEC</systemColorPalette4>
   </variables>
   <language name="es_ES">
      <variables>
         <systemDescription>El Atari ST es una línea de computadoras personales de Atari Corporation y el sucesor de la familia Atari de 8 bits. El modelo inicial, el 520ST, tuvo una distribución limitada entre abril y junio de 1985 y estuvo ampliamente disponible en julio. El 520ST es la primera computadora personal que incluye una interfaz gráfica de usuario a color con mapa de bits, utilizando una versión del GEM de Digital Research lanzada en febrero de 1985. El 1040ST, lanzado en 1986, es la primera computadora personal en enviar con un megabyte de RAM en la configuración base y también la primera con un costo por kilobyte inferior a $1 USD.

El Atari ST es parte de una generación de computadoras personales de mediados de la década de 1980 que tienen procesadores de 16 o 32 bits, 256 KB o más de RAM y interfaces gráficas de usuario controladas por mouse. Esta generación incluye el Macintosh, Amiga, Apple IIGS y, en algunos mercados, el Acorn Archimedes. "ST" oficialmente significa "Dieciséis/Treinta y dos", que se refiere al bus externo de 16 bits del Motorola 68000 y sus 32 bits internos.

El ST se vendió con el monitor a color de Atari o el monitor monocromático, que era más barato. Los modos gráficos a color del sistema solo están disponibles en el primero, mientras que el modo de mayor resolución requiere el monitor monocromático.</systemDescription>
         <systemReleaseDateFormated>1 de junio de 1985</systemReleaseDateFormated>
         <systemHardwareType>Computadora</systemHardwareType>
      </variables>
   </language>
</theme>