<theme>
   <variables>
      <systemName>CreatiVision</systemName>
      <systemDescription>The Video Technology CreatiVision is a hybrid computer and home video game console introduced by VTech in 1981 and released in 1982 during the Second generation of video game consoles. It was built by the Finnish company Salora. It cost $295 Australian Dollars. The hybrid unit was similar in concept to computers such as the APF Imagination Machine, the older VideoBrain Family Computer, and to a lesser extent the Intellivision game console and Coleco Adam computer, all of which anticipated the trend of video game consoles becoming more like low-end computers. It was discontinue in 1986.</systemDescription>
      <systemManufacturer>VTech</systemManufacturer>
      <systemReleaseYear>1982</systemReleaseYear>
      <systemReleaseDate>1982</systemReleaseDate>
      <systemReleaseDateFormated>1982</systemReleaseDateFormated>
      <systemHardwareType>Console</systemHardwareType>
      <systemCoverSize>3-4</systemCoverSize>
      <systemColor>D59234</systemColor>
      <systemColorPalette1>CCA656</systemColorPalette1>
      <systemColorPalette2>9F7C64</systemColorPalette2>
      <systemColorPalette3>E0CC75</systemColorPalette3>
      <systemColorPalette4>F09734</systemColorPalette4>
   </variables>
   <language name="es_ES">
      <variables>
         <systemDescription>El Video Technology CreatiVision es un híbrido entre computadora y consola de videojuegos doméstica introducido por VTech en 1981 y lanzado en 1982 durante la segunda generación de consolas de videojuegos. Fue fabricado por la empresa finlandesa Salora y tenía un costo de 295 dólares australianos. La unidad híbrida era similar en concepto a computadoras como la APF Imagination Machine, la VideoBrain Family Computer más antigua y, en menor medida, la consola de juegos Intellivision y la computadora Coleco Adam, todas ellas anticipando la tendencia de las consolas de videojuegos a convertirse en computadoras de gama baja. Fue descontinuado en 1986.</systemDescription>
         <systemReleaseDateFormated>1982</systemReleaseDateFormated>
         <systemHardwareType>Consola</systemHardwareType>
      </variables>
   </language>
</theme>