<theme>
   <variables>
      <systemName>Epic Games Store</systemName>
      <systemDescription>The Epic Games Store is a digital video game storefront for Microsoft Windows and macOS, operated by Epic Games. It launched in December 2018 as both a website and a standalone launcher, of which the latter is required to download and play games. The storefront provides a basic catalog, friends list management, matchmaking, and other features. Epic Games has further plans to expand the feature set of the storefront but it does not plan to add as many features as other digital distribution platforms, such as discussion boards or user reviews, instead using existing social media platforms to support these.</systemDescription>
      <systemManufacturer>Epic</systemManufacturer>
      <systemReleaseYear>2018</systemReleaseYear>
      <systemReleaseDate>2018-12</systemReleaseDate>
      <systemReleaseDateFormated>December 2018</systemReleaseDateFormated>
      <systemHardwareType>Folder</systemHardwareType>
      <systemCoverSize>3-4</systemCoverSize>
      <systemColor>8BA7AE</systemColor>
      <systemColorPalette1>FFFFFF</systemColorPalette1>
      <systemColorPalette2>777777</systemColorPalette2>
      <systemColorPalette3>343434</systemColorPalette3>
      <systemColorPalette4>35C4EE</systemColorPalette4>
   </variables>
   <language name="es_ES">
      <variables>
         <systemDescription>La Epic Games Store es una tienda digital de videojuegos para Microsoft Windows y macOS, operada por Epic Games. Se lanzó en diciembre de 2018 como un sitio web y un lanzador independiente, este último necesario para descargar y jugar los juegos. La tienda ofrece un catálogo básico, gestión de listas de amigos, emparejamiento y otras funciones. Epic Games tiene planes de ampliar las características de la tienda, pero no planea agregar tantas funciones como otras plataformas de distribución digital, como foros de discusión o reseñas de usuarios, en su lugar usa plataformas de redes sociales existentes para brindar soporte.</systemDescription>
         <systemReleaseDateFormated>Diciembre de 2018</systemReleaseDateFormated>
         <systemHardwareType>Carpeta</systemHardwareType>
      </variables>
   </language>
</theme>