<theme>
   <variables>
      <systemName>Famicom</systemName>
      <systemDescription>The Family Computer (ファミリーコンピュータ) or Famicom (ファミコン) hit the Japanese gaming market in 1983. The brainchild of Masayuki Uemura, Famicom was Nintendo’s first cartridge-based home video game console. It became an instant hit, with game titles like legendary designer Shigeru Miyamoto’s arcade classic Donkey Kong fueling sales.

The Famicom began life as the “GameCom” before system designer Masayuki Uemura’s wife suggested the moniker we know and love today. During development several ideas were bandied about, including the concept of creating a powerful home computer complete with a keyboard and disk drive, but ultimately the console became the diminutive red-and-white wonder that has become so iconic over the years; the colour scheme was apparently chosen by Nintendo president Hiroshi Yamauchi after he spotted a billboard advertisement which used the same hues.

The Famicom was designed to be both cheap and impressive. Nintendo aimed to be thrifty where possible but did not want to sacrifice performance. The aim was for their console to be unsurpassed in terms of quality and cost-effectiveness by their competitors for at least a year, if not longer. The console was purposefully designed to look like a toy – with a design scheme similar to the Game and Watch series of portable games they had released a couple of years prior to the Famicom.

The only direct competition to the Famicom was Sega’s SG-1000, which the Famicom was easily outselling. Within two years the Famicom had already sold 2.5 million units in Japan. This success emboldened Nintendo, who started to look towards international markets. Overall Nintendo sold more than 10 million units in Japan.</systemDescription>
      <systemDescriptionSource>https://www.museumofplay.org/blog/first-there-was-famicom/, https://retrogaming.tech.blog/2016/12/03/a-history-of-the-nintendo-famicom/, https://www.nintendolife.com/news/2013/07/feature_the_history_of_the_famicom_the_console_that_changed_nintendos_fortunes</systemDescriptionSource>
      <systemManufacturer>Nintendo</systemManufacturer>
      <systemReleaseYear>1983</systemReleaseYear>
      <systemReleaseDate>1983-07-15</systemReleaseDate>
      <systemReleaseDateFormated>July 15, 1983</systemReleaseDateFormated>
      <systemHardwareType>Console</systemHardwareType>
      <systemCoverSize>4-3</systemCoverSize>
      <systemColor>B93041</systemColor>
      <systemColorPalette1>EA2C27</systemColorPalette1>
      <systemColorPalette2>E6E7E8</systemColorPalette2>
      <systemColorPalette3>C0A987</systemColorPalette3>
      <systemColorPalette4>AA1A41</systemColorPalette4>
   </variables>
   <language name="es_ES">
      <variables>
         <systemDescription>La Family Computer (ファミリーコンピュータ) o Famicom (ファミコン) llegó al mercado japonés de videojuegos en 1983. La idea de Masayuki Uemura, Famicom fue la primera consola de videojuegos doméstica basada en cartuchos de Nintendo. Se convirtió en un éxito instantáneo, con títulos como el clásico de arcade Donkey Kong, diseñado por el legendario Shigeru Miyamoto, impulsando las ventas.

El Famicom comenzó su vida como el "GameCom" antes de que la esposa del diseñador del sistema, Masayuki Uemura, sugiriera el nombre que conocemos y amamos hoy en día. Durante el desarrollo, se barajaron varias ideas, incluido el concepto de crear una poderosa computadora doméstica completa con un teclado y unidad de disco, pero finalmente la consola se convirtió en la diminuta maravilla rojo y blanca que ha sido tan icónica a lo largo de los años; el esquema de colores aparentemente fue elegido por el presidente de Nintendo, Hiroshi Yamauchi, después de ver un cartel publicitario que usaba los mismos tonos.

El Famicom fue diseñado para ser barato e impresionante. Nintendo pretendía ser frugal cuando fuera posible, pero no quería sacrificar el rendimiento. El objetivo era que su consola no fuera superada en términos de calidad y rentabilidad por sus competidores durante al menos un año, si no más. La consola fue deliberadamente diseñada para parecerse a un juguete, con un esquema de diseño similar a la serie Game and Watch de juegos portátiles que habían lanzado un par de años antes del Famicom.

La única competencia directa del Famicom era el SG-1000 de Sega, que el Famicom estaba superando fácilmente en ventas. En dos años, el Famicom ya había vendido 2,5 millones de unidades en Japón. Este éxito impulsó a Nintendo, que comenzó a mirar hacia los mercados internacionales. En total, Nintendo vendió más de 10 millones de unidades en Japón.</systemDescription>
         <systemDescriptionSource>https://www.museumofplay.org/blog/first-there-was-famicom/, https://retrogaming.tech.blog/2016/12/03/a-history-of-the-nintendo-famicom/, https://www.nintendolife.com/news/2013/07/feature_the_history_of_the_famicom_the_console_that_changed_nintendos_fortunes</systemDescriptionSource>
         <systemReleaseDateFormated>15 de julio de 1983</systemReleaseDateFormated>
         <systemHardwareType>Consola</systemHardwareType>
      </variables>
   </language>
</theme>