<theme>
   <variables>
      <systemName>FinalBurn Neo</systemName>
      <systemDescription>FinalBurn Neo is a Multiple Arcade Emulator most popular for emulating Neo-Geo, Capcom, Konami, and Cave games. It is developed by the FinalBurn team and originated from FinalBurn by Dave and old MAME versions.

FinalBurn Neo is an active fork of the FinalBurn Alpha emulator, created by many of the former FBA developers.

The reason for the separation of the older branch, FB Alpha, and new spin-off branch, FB Neo, was due to an apparent disagreement between one Barry Harris and the rest of the main FBA team members over a licensing issue.</systemDescription>
      <systemManufacturer>FBA Team</systemManufacturer>
      <systemReleaseYear>2002</systemReleaseYear>
      <systemReleaseDate>2002</systemReleaseDate>
      <systemReleaseDateFormated>2002</systemReleaseDateFormated>
      <systemHardwareType>Emulator</systemHardwareType>
      <systemCoverSize>3-4</systemCoverSize>
      <systemColor>5B60B7</systemColor>
      <systemColorPalette1>C0392B</systemColorPalette1>
      <systemColorPalette2>CF8A61</systemColorPalette2>
      <systemColorPalette3>231F20</systemColorPalette3>
      <systemColorPalette4>FFFFFF</systemColorPalette4>
   </variables>
   <language name="es_ES">
      <variables>
         <systemDescription>FinalBurn Neo es un emulador múltiple de arcade, más popular por emular juegos de Neo-Geo, Capcom, Konami y Cave. Es desarrollado por el equipo de FinalBurn y originado de FinalBurn de Dave y versiones antiguas de MAME.

FinalBurn Neo es una bifurcación activa del emulador FinalBurn Alpha, creada por muchos de los antiguos desarrolladores de FBA.

La razón de la separación entre la antigua rama, FB Alpha, y la nueva rama derivada, FB Neo, fue debido a un aparente desacuerdo entre Barry Harris y el resto de los miembros principales del equipo FBA sobre un problema de licencias.</systemDescription>
         <systemReleaseDateFormated>2002</systemReleaseDateFormated>
         <systemHardwareType>Emulador</systemHardwareType>
      </variables>
   </language>
</theme>