<theme>
   <variables>
      <systemName>FM Towns</systemName>
      <systemDescription>The FM Towns (Japanese: エフエムタウンズ, Hepburn: Efu Emu Taunzu) is a Japanese personal computer built by Fujitsu from February 1989 to the summer of 1997. It started as a proprietary PC variant intended for multimedia applications and PC games, but later became more compatible with IBM PC compatibles. In 1993, the FM Towns Marty was released, a game console compatible with existing FM Towns games.

The "FM" part of the name means "Fujitsu Micro" like their earlier products, while the "Towns" part is derived from the code name the system was assigned while in development, "Townes". This refers to Charles Townes, one of the winners of the 1964 Nobel Prize in Physics, following a custom of Fujitsu at the time to code name PC products after Nobel Prize winners. The e in "Townes" was dropped when the system went into production to make it clearer that the term was to be pronounced like the word "towns" rather than the potential "tow-nes".</systemDescription>
      <systemManufacturer>Fujitsu</systemManufacturer>
      <systemReleaseYear>1989</systemReleaseYear>
      <systemReleaseDate>1989-02-28</systemReleaseDate>
      <systemReleaseDateFormated>February 28, 1989</systemReleaseDateFormated>
      <systemHardwareType>Computer</systemHardwareType>
      <systemCoverSize>3-4</systemCoverSize>
      <systemColor>6F90FE</systemColor>
      <systemColorPalette1>9D9D9D</systemColorPalette1>
      <systemColorPalette2>009971</systemColorPalette2>
      <systemColorPalette3>606875</systemColorPalette3>
      <systemColorPalette4>151619</systemColorPalette4>
   </variables>
   <language name="es_ES">
      <variables>
         <systemDescription>El FM Towns (japonés: エフエムタウンズ, Hepburn: Efu Emu Taunzu) es una computadora personal japonesa fabricada por Fujitsu desde febrero de 1989 hasta el verano de 1997. Comenzó como una variante de PC propietaria destinada a aplicaciones multimedia y videojuegos de PC, pero más tarde se hizo más compatible con los PC compatibles con IBM. En 1993, se lanzó el FM Towns Marty, una consola de videojuegos compatible con los juegos existentes de FM Towns.

La parte "FM" del nombre significa "Fujitsu Micro", como sus productos anteriores, mientras que la parte "Towns" se deriva del nombre en código que se le asignó al sistema durante el desarrollo, "Townes". Esto hace referencia a Charles Townes, uno de los ganadores del Premio Nobel de Física en 1964, siguiendo una costumbre de Fujitsu en ese momento de nombrar sus productos informáticos con nombres de ganadores del Premio Nobel. La "e" en "Townes" se eliminó cuando el sistema entró en producción para que fuera más claro que el término debía pronunciarse como la palabra "towns" y no como "tow-nes".</systemDescription>
         <systemReleaseDateFormated>28 de febrero de 1989</systemReleaseDateFormated>
         <systemHardwareType>Computadora</systemHardwareType>
      </variables>
   </language>
</theme>