<theme>
   <variables>
      <systemName>Game Gear</systemName>
      <systemDescription>The Game Gear is an 8-bit fourth generation handheld game console released by Sega on October 6, 1990 in Japan, in April 1991 throughout North America and Europe, and during 1992 in Australia. The Game Gear primarily competed with Nintendo's Game Boy, the Atari Lynx, and NEC's TurboExpress. It shares much of its hardware with the Master System, and can play Master System games by the use of an adapter. Sega positioned the Game Gear, which had a full-color backlit screen with a landscape format, as a technologically superior handheld to the Game Boy.

Though the Game Gear was rushed to market, its unique game library and price point gave it an edge over the Atari Lynx and TurboExpress. However, due to its short battery life, lack of original games, and weak support from Sega, the Game Gear was unable to surpass the Game Boy, selling 10.62 million units by March 1996. The Game Gear was discontinued on April 30, 1997. It was re-released as a budget system by Majesco Entertainment in 2000, under license from Sega.</systemDescription>
      <systemManufacturer>Sega</systemManufacturer>
      <systemReleaseYear>1990</systemReleaseYear>
      <systemReleaseDate>1990-10-06</systemReleaseDate>
      <systemReleaseDateFormated>October 6, 1990</systemReleaseDateFormated>
      <systemHardwareType>Portable</systemHardwareType>
      <systemCoverSize>3-4</systemCoverSize>
      <systemColor>356FAF</systemColor>
      <systemColorPalette1>CCCBCB</systemColorPalette1>
      <systemColorPalette2>D41808</systemColorPalette2>
      <systemColorPalette3>008200</systemColorPalette3>
      <systemColorPalette4>0000FE</systemColorPalette4>
   </variables>
   <language name="es_ES">
      <variables>
         <systemDescription>El Game Gear es una consola de videojuegos portátil de 8 bits de cuarta generación lanzada por Sega el 6 de octubre de 1990 en Japón, en abril de 1991 en América del Norte y Europa, y en 1992 en Australia. El Game Gear compitió principalmente con el Game Boy de Nintendo, el Atari Lynx y el TurboExpress de NEC. Comparte gran parte de su hardware con el Master System y puede jugar juegos de Master System mediante un adaptador. Sega posicionó el Game Gear, que tenía una pantalla a color retroiluminada en formato paisaje, como una consola portátil tecnológicamente superior al Game Boy.

Aunque el Game Gear fue apresurado al mercado, su biblioteca de juegos única y su precio le dieron una ventaja sobre el Atari Lynx y el TurboExpress. Sin embargo, debido a su corta duración de batería, falta de juegos originales y un apoyo débil por parte de Sega, el Game Gear no pudo superar al Game Boy, vendiendo 10.62 millones de unidades para marzo de 1996. El Game Gear fue descontinuado el 30 de abril de 1997. Fue relanzado como un sistema de bajo costo por Majesco Entertainment en 2000, bajo licencia de Sega.</systemDescription>
         <systemReleaseDateFormated>6 de octubre de 1990</systemReleaseDateFormated>
         <systemHardwareType>Consola portátil</systemHardwareType>
      </variables>
   </language>
</theme>