<theme>
   <variables>
      <systemName>Mega Duck</systemName>
      <systemDescription>The Welback Holdings Mega Duck, usually just referred to as Mega Duck, is a fourth generation (1987-2004) handheld video game console developed and distributed by Welback Holdings, but marketed under different names like Creatronic, Videojet, Cougar USA, and Hartung. It was released in August 1993 in Netherlands at a retail price of fl 129 as the Creatronic Mega Duck. The console was also released in Germany (1993) distributed by Hartung, France (1993) distributed by Videojet, and Brazil (1993) but as the Cougar USA Cougar Boy. The Mega Duck was an obvious clone of the Game Boy in looks, and it sadly lacked any innovative games to set it apart to become a competitor. The console was discontinued quietly sometime in early 1995.</systemDescription>
      <systemManufacturer>Welback Holdings</systemManufacturer>
      <systemReleaseYear>1993</systemReleaseYear>
      <systemReleaseDate>1993</systemReleaseDate>
      <systemReleaseDateFormated>1993</systemReleaseDateFormated>
      <systemHardwareType>Portable</systemHardwareType>
      <systemCoverSize>4-3</systemCoverSize>
      <systemColor>17999A</systemColor>
      <systemColorPalette1>415E81</systemColorPalette1>
      <systemColorPalette2>EAEAEA</systemColorPalette2>
      <systemColorPalette3>51BABB</systemColorPalette3>
      <systemColorPalette4>819B73</systemColorPalette4>
   </variables>
   <language name="es_ES">
      <variables>
         <systemDescription>El Welback Holdings Mega Duck, generalmente conocido simplemente como Mega Duck, es una consola de videojuegos portátil de cuarta generación (1987-2004) desarrollada y distribuida por Welback Holdings, pero comercializada bajo diferentes nombres como Creatronic, Videojet, Cougar USA y Hartung. Fue lanzada en agosto de 1993 en los Países Bajos a un precio minorista de 129 florines como el Creatronic Mega Duck. La consola también se lanzó en Alemania (1993), distribuida por Hartung; en Francia (1993), distribuida por Videojet; y en Brasil (1993) bajo el nombre Cougar USA Cougar Boy. El Mega Duck era una evidente copia del Game Boy en apariencia, y carecía de juegos innovadores que lo destacaran como competidor. La consola fue descontinuada silenciosamente a principios de 1995.</systemDescription>
         <systemReleaseDateFormated>1993</systemReleaseDateFormated>
         <systemHardwareType>Portátil</systemHardwareType>
      </variables>
   </language>
</theme>