<theme>
   <variables>
      <systemName>MESS</systemName>
      <systemDescription>Multi Emulator Super System (MESS) is an emulator for various consoles and computer systems, based on the MAME core. It used to be a standalone program (which has since been discontinued), but is now integrated into MAME (which is actively developed). MESS emulates portable and console gaming systems, computer platforms, and calculators. The project strives for accuracy and portability and therefore is not always the fastest emulator for any one particular system. Its accuracy makes it also useful for homebrew game development.</systemDescription>
      <systemManufacturer>MESS Team</systemManufacturer>
      <systemReleaseYear>1998</systemReleaseYear>
      <systemReleaseDate>1998</systemReleaseDate>
      <systemReleaseDateFormated>1998</systemReleaseDateFormated>
      <systemHardwareType>Emulator</systemHardwareType>
      <systemCoverSize>3-4</systemCoverSize>
      <systemColor>5B60B7</systemColor>
      <systemColorPalette1>FFA102</systemColorPalette1>
      <systemColorPalette2>A05F00</systemColorPalette2>
      <systemColorPalette3>FFEFD5</systemColorPalette3>
      <systemColorPalette4>FFD183</systemColorPalette4>
   </variables>
   <language name="es_ES">
      <variables>
         <systemDescription>Multi Emulator Super System (MESS) es un emulador para varias consolas y sistemas informáticos, basado en el núcleo de MAME. Antes era un programa independiente (que ya ha sido descontinuado), pero ahora está integrado en MAME (que sigue en desarrollo). MESS emula sistemas de juegos portátiles y de consola, plataformas informáticas y calculadoras. El proyecto se enfoca en la precisión y la portabilidad, por lo que no siempre es el emulador más rápido para un sistema en particular. Su precisión también lo hace útil para el desarrollo de juegos caseros.</systemDescription>
         <systemReleaseDateFormated>1998</systemReleaseDateFormated>
         <systemHardwareType>Emulador</systemHardwareType>
      </variables>
   </language>
</theme>