<theme>
   <variables>
      <systemName>Nintendo Entertainment System</systemName>
      <systemDescription>The history of the Nintendo Entertainment System (NES) spans the 1982 development of the Family Computer, to the 1985 launch of the NES, to Nintendo's rise to global dominance based upon this platform throughout the late 1980s. The Family Computer (ファミリーコンピュータ) or Famicom (ファミコン) was developed in 1982 and launched in 1983 in Japan. Following the North American video game crash of 1983, the Famicom was adapted into the NES which was launched in North America in 1985. Transitioning the company from its arcade game history into this combined global 8-bit home video game console platform, the Famicom and NES continued to aggressively compete with the next-generation 16-bit consoles including the 1988 Sega Genesis. The platform was succeeded by the Super Famicom in 1990 and the Super Nintendo Entertainment System in 1991, but its support and production continued until 1995. Interest in the NES has been renewed by collectors and emulators, including Nintendo's own Virtual Console platform.</systemDescription>
      <systemDescriptionSource>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/History_of_the_Nintendo_Entertainment_System</systemDescriptionSource>
      <systemManufacturer>Nintendo</systemManufacturer>
      <systemReleaseYear>1985</systemReleaseYear>
      <systemReleaseDate>1985-10-18</systemReleaseDate>
      <systemReleaseDateFormated>October 18, 1985</systemReleaseDateFormated>
      <systemHardwareType>Console</systemHardwareType>
      <systemCoverSize>3-4</systemCoverSize>
      <systemColor>B93041</systemColor>
      <systemColorPalette1>CD3332</systemColorPalette1>
      <systemColorPalette2>FFFFFF</systemColorPalette2>
      <systemColorPalette3>666666</systemColorPalette3>
      <systemColorPalette4>212121</systemColorPalette4>
   </variables>
   <language name="es_ES">
      <variables>
         <systemDescription>La historia de la Nintendo Entertainment System (NES) abarca desde el desarrollo de la Family Computer en 1982, hasta el lanzamiento de la NES en 1985 y el ascenso de Nintendo a la dominación global basada en esta plataforma a finales de la década de 1980. La Family Computer (ファミリーコンピュータ) o Famicom (ファミコン) fue desarrollada en 1982 y lanzada en 1983 en Japón. Tras el colapso de la industria de los videojuegos en Norteamérica en 1983, el Famicom fue adaptado como la NES, que se lanzó en Norteamérica en 1985. Al hacer la transición de la compañía desde su historia en los juegos arcade hacia esta plataforma global de consola de videojuegos doméstica de 8 bits, el Famicom y la NES continuaron compitiendo agresivamente con las consolas de próxima generación de 16 bits, incluida la Sega Genesis de 1988. La plataforma fue sucedida por la Super Famicom en 1990 y la Super Nintendo Entertainment System en 1991, pero su soporte y producción continuaron hasta 1995. El interés en la NES ha resurgido gracias a coleccionistas y emuladores, incluida la propia plataforma Virtual Console de Nintendo.</systemDescription>
         <systemReleaseDateFormated>18 de octubre de 1985</systemReleaseDateFormated>
         <systemHardwareType>Consola</systemHardwareType>
      </variables>
   </language>
</theme>