<theme>
   <variables>
      <systemName>Neo Geo Pocket</systemName>
      <systemDescription>The Neo Geo Pocket is a monochrome handheld game console released by SNK. It was the company's first handheld system and is part of the Neo Geo family. It debuted in Japan in late 1998 but never saw an American release, being exclusive to Japan, Asia and Europe.

The Neo Geo Pocket is considered to be an unsuccessful console. Lower than expected sales resulted in its discontinuation in 1999, and was immediately succeeded by the Neo Geo Pocket Color, a full color device allowing the system to compete more easily with the dominant Game Boy Color handheld, and which also saw an American release. Though the system enjoyed only a short life, there were some significant games released on the system such as Samurai Shodown, and King of Fighters R-1.</systemDescription>
      <systemManufacturer>SNK</systemManufacturer>
      <systemReleaseYear>1998</systemReleaseYear>
      <systemReleaseDate>1998-12-31</systemReleaseDate>
      <systemReleaseDateFormated>December 31, 1998</systemReleaseDateFormated>
      <systemHardwareType>Portable</systemHardwareType>
      <systemCoverSize>1-1</systemCoverSize>
      <systemColor>ECA045</systemColor>
      <systemColorPalette1>B2B8BD</systemColorPalette1>
      <systemColorPalette2>E92A30</systemColorPalette2>
      <systemColorPalette3>25374A</systemColorPalette3>
      <systemColorPalette4>0F1520</systemColorPalette4>
   </variables>
   <language name="es_ES">
      <variables>
         <systemDescription>La Neo Geo Pocket es una consola de videojuegos portátil monocromática lanzada por SNK. Fue la primera consola portátil de la compañía y forma parte de la familia Neo Geo. Debutó en Japón a finales de 1998, pero nunca tuvo un lanzamiento en América, siendo exclusiva de Japón, Asia y Europa.

La Neo Geo Pocket es considerada una consola poco exitosa. Las ventas fueron más bajas de lo esperado, lo que llevó a su descontinuación en 1999 y a su sucesora inmediata, la Neo Geo Pocket Color, un dispositivo a todo color que permitió que el sistema compitiera más fácilmente con la dominante Game Boy Color y que sí tuvo un lanzamiento en América. Aunque el sistema tuvo una vida corta, se lanzaron algunos juegos importantes en la plataforma, como Samurai Shodown y King of Fighters R-1.</systemDescription>
         <systemReleaseDateFormated>31 de diciembre de 1998</systemReleaseDateFormated>
         <systemHardwareType>Consola portátil</systemHardwareType>
      </variables>
   </language>
</theme>