<theme>
   <variables>
      <systemName>PC-98</systemName>
      <systemDescription>The NEC PC-9800 was line of personal computers developed in 1982 in Japan by NEC Corporation based on IBM, aimed exclusively at the Japanese market.

The first model was a 16-bit architecture with an Intel 8086 processor clocked at 5 MHz and 128 KB of RAM. It shipped with graphics cards capable of displaying 8 colors at 640x400 resolution - a clear performance differentiator compared to PCs of the time.

Initially conceived as a solution for industrial and office applications, by 1987 the PC-9801 series captured nearly 90% of the Japanese personal computer market. Over time, as power increased and graphics and sound effects were appreciated by home users (especially gamers), it also became popular for non-commercial applications - the Touhou Project series, for example, made its debut.</systemDescription>
      <systemManufacturer>NEC</systemManufacturer>
      <systemReleaseYear>1982</systemReleaseYear>
      <systemReleaseDate>1982-10-01</systemReleaseDate>
      <systemReleaseDateFormated>October 1, 1982</systemReleaseDateFormated>
      <systemHardwareType>Computer</systemHardwareType>
      <systemCoverSize>3-4</systemCoverSize>
      <systemColor>5185B2</systemColor>
      <systemColorPalette1>951610</systemColorPalette1>
      <systemColorPalette2>16643C</systemColorPalette2>
      <systemColorPalette3>00499A</systemColorPalette3>
      <systemColorPalette4>3B3431</systemColorPalette4>
   </variables>
   <language name="es_ES">
      <variables>
         <systemDescription>La NEC PC-9800 fue una línea de computadoras personales desarrollada en 1982 en Japón por NEC Corporation, basada en la arquitectura de IBM y dirigida exclusivamente al mercado japonés.

El primer modelo tenía una arquitectura de 16 bits con un procesador Intel 8086 a 5 MHz y 128 KB de RAM. Venía con tarjetas gráficas capaces de mostrar 8 colores a una resolución de 640x400, lo que representaba una clara ventaja de rendimiento en comparación con las PC de la época.

Inicialmente concebida como una solución para aplicaciones industriales y de oficina, en 1987 la serie PC-9801 capturó casi el 90% del mercado japonés de computadoras personales. Con el tiempo, a medida que la potencia aumentó y los gráficos y efectos de sonido fueron apreciados por los usuarios domésticos (especialmente los jugadores), también se volvió popular para aplicaciones no comerciales. La serie Touhou Project, por ejemplo, debutó en esta plataforma.</systemDescription>
         <systemReleaseDateFormated>1 de octubre de 1982</systemReleaseDateFormated>
         <systemHardwareType>Computadora</systemHardwareType>
      </variables>
   </language>
</theme>