<theme>
   <variables>
      <systemName>PC-FX</systemName>
      <systemDescription>The PC-FX is a 32-bit home video game console developed by both NEC and Hudson Soft and released in Japan in 1994. Powered by an NEC V810 CPU and using CD-ROMs, the PC-FX was intended as the successor to the PC Engine and its international counterpart the TurboGrafx-16, two successful video game consoles from the late 1980s. It is NEC's final foray into the home console market.

The console is shaped like a tower PC and was meant to be similarly upgradeable. However the PC-FX lacked a 3D polygon-based graphics chip which rendered the system underpowered in comparison to its competitors. It was also expensive and lacked developer support, and as a result it was unable to compete effectively with its fifth generation peers. The PC-FX was NEC's last home video game console, and was discontinued in February 1998. It was considered a commercial failure.</systemDescription>
      <systemManufacturer>NEC</systemManufacturer>
      <systemReleaseYear>1994</systemReleaseYear>
      <systemReleaseDate>1994-12-23</systemReleaseDate>
      <systemReleaseDateFormated>December 23, 1994</systemReleaseDateFormated>
      <systemHardwareType>Console</systemHardwareType>
      <systemCoverSize>3-4</systemCoverSize>
      <systemColor>9378DA</systemColor>
      <systemColorPalette1>FEC101</systemColorPalette1>
      <systemColorPalette2>01015B</systemColorPalette2>
      <systemColorPalette3>5C3073</systemColorPalette3>
      <systemColorPalette4>F00020</systemColorPalette4>
   </variables>
   <language name="es_ES">
      <variables>
         <systemDescription>La PC-FX es una consola de videojuegos doméstica de 32 bits desarrollada por NEC y Hudson Soft, lanzada en Japón en 1994. Impulsada por una CPU NEC V810 y utilizando CD-ROMs, la PC-FX estaba destinada a ser la sucesora de la PC Engine y su contraparte internacional, la TurboGrafx-16, dos consolas de videojuegos exitosas de finales de la década de 1980. Fue el último intento de NEC en el mercado de consolas domésticas.

La consola tiene la forma de una torre de PC y estaba diseñada para ser actualizable de manera similar. Sin embargo, la PC-FX carecía de un chip gráfico basado en polígonos 3D, lo que la dejó en desventaja en comparación con sus competidores. Además, era costosa y carecía de apoyo por parte de los desarrolladores, por lo que no pudo competir eficazmente con sus rivales de la quinta generación. La PC-FX fue la última consola de videojuegos doméstica de NEC y fue descontinuada en febrero de 1998. Se considera un fracaso comercial.</systemDescription>
         <systemReleaseDateFormated>23 de diciembre de 1994</systemReleaseDateFormated>
         <systemHardwareType>Consola</systemHardwareType>
      </variables>
   </language>
</theme>