<theme>
   <variables>
      <systemName>ST-V</systemName>
      <systemDescription>ST-V (Sega Titan Video) is an arcade system board released by Sega, in 1994 for Japan and 1995 worldwide. Departing from their usual process of building custom arcade hardware, Sega's ST-V is essentially identical to the Sega Saturn home console system. The only difference is the media; ST-V used ROM cartridges instead of CD-ROM discs to store games, with the exception of Sports Fishing 2. Being derived from the Saturn hardware, the ST-V was presumably named after the moon Titan, a satellite of Saturn.

The majority of ST-V titles were released only in Japan, but a notable exception was the port of Dynamite Deka, which became Die Hard Arcade. Games released for the ST-V include the arcade versions of Virtua Fighter Remix, Radiant Silvergun, Golden Axe: The Duel, and Final Fight Revenge. The shared hardware between Saturn and ST-V allowed for very "pure" ports for the Saturn console.</systemDescription>
      <systemManufacturer>Sega</systemManufacturer>
      <systemReleaseYear>1994</systemReleaseYear>
      <systemReleaseDate>1994</systemReleaseDate>
      <systemReleaseDateFormated>1994</systemReleaseDateFormated>
      <systemHardwareType>Arcade</systemHardwareType>
      <systemCoverSize>3-4</systemCoverSize>
      <systemColor>4A529D</systemColor>
      <systemColorPalette1>034693</systemColorPalette1>
      <systemColorPalette2>F7ED18</systemColorPalette2>
      <systemColorPalette3>F4133D</systemColorPalette3>
      <systemColorPalette4>199A40</systemColorPalette4>
   </variables>
   <language name="es_ES">
      <variables>
         <systemDescription>ST-V (Sega Titan Video) es una placa de sistema arcade lanzada por Sega en 1994 en Japón y en 1995 a nivel mundial. A diferencia de su proceso habitual de construir hardware arcade personalizado, el ST-V de Sega es esencialmente idéntico a la consola doméstica Sega Saturn. La única diferencia es el medio de almacenamiento; el ST-V utilizaba cartuchos ROM en lugar de discos CD-ROM para almacenar los juegos, con la excepción de Sports Fishing 2. Al derivarse del hardware de la Saturn, se presume que el nombre ST-V hace referencia a la luna Titán, un satélite de Saturno.

La mayoría de los títulos del ST-V fueron lanzados solo en Japón, pero una notable excepción fue la versión arcade de Dynamite Deka, que se convirtió en Die Hard Arcade. Entre los juegos lanzados para el ST-V se encuentran las versiones arcade de Virtua Fighter Remix, Radiant Silvergun, Golden Axe: The Duel y Final Fight Revenge. El hardware compartido entre la Saturn y el ST-V permitió la creación de ports muy fieles para la consola Saturn.</systemDescription>
         <systemReleaseDateFormated>1994</systemReleaseDateFormated>
         <systemHardwareType>Arcade</systemHardwareType>
      </variables>
   </language>
</theme>