<theme>
   <variables>
      <systemName>Symbian</systemName>
      <systemDescription>Symbian is a discontinued mobile operating system (OS) and computing platform designed for smartphones. It was originally developed as a proprietary software OS for personal digital assistants in 1998 by the Symbian Ltd. consortium. Symbian OS is a descendant of Psion's EPOC, and was released exclusively on ARM processors, although an unreleased x86 port existed. Symbian was used by many major mobile phone brands, like Samsung, Motorola, Sony Ericsson, and above all by Nokia. It was also prevalent in Japan by brands including Fujitsu, Sharp and Mitsubishi. As a pioneer that established the smartphone industry, it was the most popular smartphone OS on a worldwide average until the end of 2010, at a time when smartphones were in limited use, when it was overtaken by iOS and Android. It was notably less popular in North America.</systemDescription>
      <systemManufacturer>Symbian Ltd.</systemManufacturer>
      <systemReleaseYear>1997</systemReleaseYear>
      <systemReleaseDate>1997-06-05</systemReleaseDate>
      <systemReleaseDateFormated>June 5, 1997</systemReleaseDateFormated>
      <systemHardwareType>OS</systemHardwareType>
      <systemCoverSize>1-1</systemCoverSize>
      <systemColor>222222</systemColor>
      <systemColorPalette1>0082B5</systemColorPalette1>
      <systemColorPalette2>FBAB18</systemColorPalette2>
      <systemColorPalette3>1F4394</systemColorPalette3>
      <systemColorPalette4>EE3537</systemColorPalette4>
   </variables>
   <language name="es_ES">
      <variables>
         <systemDescription>Symbian es un sistema operativo móvil (OS) y una plataforma informática discontinuada, diseñada para teléfonos inteligentes. Fue desarrollado originalmente como un sistema operativo de software propietario para asistentes digitales personales en 1998 por el consorcio Symbian Ltd. 

Symbian OS es un descendiente de EPOC de Psion y fue lanzado exclusivamente en procesadores ARM, aunque existió un puerto no publicado para x86. Symbian fue utilizado por muchas de las principales marcas de teléfonos móviles, como Samsung, Motorola, Sony Ericsson y, sobre todo, Nokia. También fue popular en Japón, siendo adoptado por marcas como Fujitsu, Sharp y Mitsubishi. 

Como pionero que estableció la industria de los teléfonos inteligentes, Symbian fue el sistema operativo de smartphones más popular a nivel mundial hasta finales de 2010, cuando los teléfonos inteligentes aún tenían un uso limitado, siendo superado posteriormente por iOS y Android. Fue notablemente menos popular en América del Norte.</systemDescription>
         <systemReleaseDateFormated>5 de junio de 1997</systemReleaseDateFormated>
         <systemHardwareType>OS</systemHardwareType>
      </variables>
   </language>
</theme>