<theme>
   <variables>
      <systemName>Thomson TO8</systemName>
      <systemDescription>The Thomson TO8 is a home computer introduced by French company Thomson SA in 1986, with a cost of 2,990 FF. It replaces its predecessor, the Thomson TO7/70, while remaining essentially compatible.  The new features of the TO8, like larger memory (256KB) and better graphics modes (powered by the Thomson EF9369 graphics chip), are shared with the other third generation Thomson computers ( MO6 and TO9+).  The TO8 has a tape drive and Microsoft BASIC 1.0 (in standard and 512 KB versions)[9] on its internal ROM, and there is an optional external floppy drive. Graphics were provided by the Thomson EF9369 chip, allowing the display of 16 colors from a palette of 4096.  More than 120 games exist for the system.</systemDescription>
      <systemManufacturer>Thomson SA</systemManufacturer>
      <systemReleaseYear>1986</systemReleaseYear>
      <systemReleaseDate>1986</systemReleaseDate>
      <systemReleaseDateFormated>1986</systemReleaseDateFormated>
      <systemHardwareType>Computer</systemHardwareType>
      <systemCoverSize>3-4</systemCoverSize>
      <systemColor>2C5299</systemColor>
      <systemColorPalette1>E6F0EF</systemColorPalette1>
      <systemColorPalette2>F0C73B</systemColorPalette2>
      <systemColorPalette3>4F8E5C</systemColorPalette3>
      <systemColorPalette4>2C2D2C</systemColorPalette4>
   </variables>
   <language name="es_ES">
      <variables>
         <systemDescription>La Thomson TO8 es una computadora doméstica introducida por la empresa francesa Thomson SA en 1986, con un costo de 2,990 FF. Reemplaza a su predecesora, la Thomson TO7/70, manteniendo esencialmente la compatibilidad. 

Las nuevas características del TO8, como una mayor memoria (256 KB) y mejores modos gráficos (impulsados por el chip gráfico Thomson EF9369), son compartidas con otras computadoras de tercera generación de Thomson (MO6 y TO9+). El TO8 incluye una unidad de casete y Microsoft BASIC 1.0 (en versiones estándar y de 512 KB) en su ROM interna, además de contar con una unidad de disquete externa opcional. Sus gráficos, proporcionados por el chip Thomson EF9369, permiten la visualización de 16 colores a partir de una paleta de 4096. Existen más de 120 juegos para el sistema.</systemDescription>
         <systemReleaseDateFormated>1986</systemReleaseDateFormated>
         <systemHardwareType>Computadora</systemHardwareType>
      </variables>
   </language>
</theme>