<theme>
   <variables>
      <systemName>Vectrex</systemName>
      <systemDescription>The Vectrex is a vector display-based home video game console–the only one ever designed and released for the home market, developed by Smith Engineering. It was first released for the North America market in November 1982 and then Europe and Japan in 1983. Originally manufactured by General Consumer Electronics, it was later licensed to Milton Bradley after they acquired the company. Bandai released the system in Japan.

The Vectrex, in contrast to other video-game systems available at the time, featured an integrated monochrome CRT monitor and did not need to be hooked up to a television set as it provided its own built-in display. A detachable wired control pad was mounted at, and could be folded into, the lower base of the console. Games included translucent color sheet overlays that could be placed over the monochrome screen. A number of peripherals were produced, such as a pair of 3D goggles known as the "3D Imager" and a "light-pen" that allowed the player to draw directly on the screen. A built-in game, Mine Storm, was playable without inserting a cartridge.</systemDescription>
      <systemManufacturer>Smith Engineering</systemManufacturer>
      <systemReleaseYear>1982</systemReleaseYear>
      <systemReleaseDate>1982-11</systemReleaseDate>
      <systemReleaseDateFormated>November 1982</systemReleaseDateFormated>
      <systemHardwareType>Console</systemHardwareType>
      <systemCoverSize>3-4</systemCoverSize>
      <systemColor>4D98D8</systemColor>
      <systemColorPalette1>EEF020</systemColorPalette1>
      <systemColorPalette2>EC1D25</systemColorPalette2>
      <systemColorPalette3>11192E</systemColorPalette3>
      <systemColorPalette4>166FC1</systemColorPalette4>
   </variables>
   <language name="es_ES">
      <variables>
         <systemDescription>La Vectrex es una consola de videojuegos doméstica basada en una pantalla de vectores, siendo la única de este tipo diseñada y lanzada para el mercado doméstico. Fue desarrollada por Smith Engineering y lanzada por primera vez en Norteamérica en noviembre de 1982, seguida por Europa y Japón en 1983. Inicialmente fue fabricada por General Consumer Electronics y posteriormente licenciada a Milton Bradley después de que adquirieran la empresa. Bandai lanzó el sistema en Japón.

A diferencia de otros sistemas de videojuegos de la época, la Vectrex incluía un monitor CRT monocromático integrado y no necesitaba conectarse a un televisor, ya que contaba con su propia pantalla incorporada. Tenía un control con cable desmontable que se almacenaba en la base inferior de la consola. Los juegos incluían hojas translúcidas de colores que podían colocarse sobre la pantalla monocromática. Se produjeron varios periféricos, como unas gafas 3D conocidas como "3D Imager" y un "light-pen" que permitía al jugador dibujar directamente en la pantalla. El juego Mine Storm venía integrado y se podía jugar sin necesidad de insertar un cartucho.</systemDescription>
         <systemReleaseDateFormated>noviembre de 1982</systemReleaseDateFormated>
         <systemHardwareType>Consola</systemHardwareType>
      </variables>
   </language>
</theme>