<theme>
   <variables>
      <systemName>VIC-20</systemName>
      <systemDescription>The Commodore VIC-20 (known as the VC-20 in Germany and the VIC-1001 in Japan) is an 8-bit home computer that was sold by Commodore Business Machines. The VIC-20 was announced in 1980, roughly three years after Commodore's first personal computer, the PET. The VIC-20 was the first computer of any description to sell one million units. It was described as "one of the first anti-spectatorial, non-esoteric computers by design...no longer relegated to hobbyist/enthusiasts or those with money, the computer Commodore developed was the computer of the future.

The VIC-20 was called VC-20 in Germany because the pronunciation of VIC with a German accent sounds like the German expletives "fick" or "wichsen". The term VC was marketed as though it was an abbreviation of VolksComputer ("people's computer," similar to Volkswagen and Volksempfänger).</systemDescription>
      <systemManufacturer>Commodore</systemManufacturer>
      <systemReleaseYear>1980</systemReleaseYear>
      <systemReleaseDate>1980-06</systemReleaseDate>
      <systemReleaseDateFormated>June 1980</systemReleaseDateFormated>
      <systemHardwareType>Computer</systemHardwareType>
      <systemCoverSize>3-4</systemCoverSize>
      <systemColor>5F8FC8</systemColor>
      <systemColorPalette1>896841</systemColorPalette1>
      <systemColorPalette2>D3D3C9</systemColorPalette2>
      <systemColorPalette3>FFCD1C</systemColorPalette3>
      <systemColorPalette4>DC2770</systemColorPalette4>
   </variables>
   <language name="es_ES">
      <variables>
         <systemDescription>La Commodore VIC-20 (conocida como VC-20 en Alemania y VIC-1001 en Japón) es una computadora doméstica de 8 bits vendida por Commodore Business Machines. La VIC-20 fue anunciada en 1980, aproximadamente tres años después de la primera computadora personal de Commodore, la PET. Fue la primera computadora de cualquier tipo en vender un millón de unidades. Fue descrita como "una de las primeras computadoras diseñadas para ser accesibles y no exclusivas... ya no relegada solo a aficionados o personas con recursos, la computadora desarrollada por Commodore era la computadora del futuro".

En Alemania, la VIC-20 fue llamada VC-20 porque la pronunciación de "VIC" con acento alemán sonaba similar a ciertas palabras vulgares en alemán. El término "VC" se comercializó como una abreviatura de "VolksComputer" ("computadora del pueblo"), en referencia a marcas como Volkswagen y Volksempfänger.</systemDescription>
         <systemReleaseDateFormated>junio de 1980</systemReleaseDateFormated>
         <systemHardwareType>Computadora</systemHardwareType>
      </variables>
   </language>
</theme>