<theme>
   <variables>
      <systemName>Virtual Boy</systemName>
      <systemDescription>The Virtual Boy is a 32-bit tabletop portable video game console developed and manufactured by Nintendo. Released in 1995, it was marketed as the first console capable of displaying stereoscopic "3D" graphics. The player uses the console like a head-mounted display, placing the head against the eyepiece to see a red monochrome display.

The games use a parallax effect to create the illusion of depth. Sales failed to meet targets, and Nintendo ceased distribution and game development in 1996, having released only 22 games for the system.</systemDescription>
      <systemManufacturer>Nintendo</systemManufacturer>
      <systemReleaseYear>1995</systemReleaseYear>
      <systemReleaseDate>1995-07-21</systemReleaseDate>
      <systemReleaseDateFormated>July 21, 1995</systemReleaseDateFormated>
      <systemHardwareType>Portable</systemHardwareType>
      <systemCoverSize>1-1</systemCoverSize>
      <systemColor>E1414A</systemColor>
      <systemColorPalette1>363636</systemColorPalette1>
      <systemColorPalette2>FE0016</systemColorPalette2>
      <systemColorPalette3>8A8C8E</systemColorPalette3>
      <systemColorPalette4>232323</systemColorPalette4>
   </variables>
   <language name="es_ES">
      <variables>
         <systemDescription>La Virtual Boy es una consola portátil de videojuegos de mesa de 32 bits desarrollada y fabricada por Nintendo. Lanzada en 1995, fue promocionada como la primera consola capaz de mostrar gráficos estereoscópicos en "3D". El jugador usa la consola como un visor montado en la cabeza, colocando los ojos contra el ocular para ver una pantalla monocromática en rojo.

Los juegos utilizan un efecto de paralaje para crear la ilusión de profundidad. Las ventas no alcanzaron los objetivos previstos, y Nintendo cesó su distribución y el desarrollo de juegos en 1996, habiendo lanzado solo 22 títulos para el sistema.</systemDescription>
         <systemReleaseDateFormated>21 de julio de 1995</systemReleaseDateFormated>
         <systemHardwareType>Consola portátil</systemHardwareType>
      </variables>
   </language>
</theme>