<theme>
   <variables>
      <systemName>X1</systemName>
      <systemDescription>The X1 (エックスワン, Ekkusuwan), sometimes called the Sharp X1, is a series of home computers released by Sharp Corporation from 1982 to 1988. It was based on a Z80 CPU.

Despite the fact that the Computer Division of Sharp Corporation had released the MZ series, suddenly the Television Division released a new computer series called the X1. At the time the original X1 was released, all other home computers generally had a BASIC language in ROM. However the X1 did not have a BASIC ROM, and it had to load the Hu-BASIC interpreter from a cassette tape. On the plus side however, this concept meant that a free RAM area was available that was as big as possible when not using BASIC. This policy was originally copied from the Sharp MZ series, and they were called clean computers in Japan. The cabinet shape of X1 was also much more stylish than others at that time and a range of cabinet colors (including Red) was selectable.

The RGB display monitor for the X1 had a television tuner, and a computer screen could be super-imposed on TV. All the TV functions could be controlled from a computer program. The character font was completely programmable (A.K.A. PCG) with 4bit color, and was effectively used in many games. The entirety of the VRAM memory was mapped on to the I/O area, so it was controlled without bank switching. Since X1 had these features, it was very powerful for game software.

While X1 was struggling to sell, the PC8801 (from NEC) was quickly becoming popular in the Japanese market. In 1984, Sharp released the X1 turbo series with high resolution graphics (640x400, while X1 had 640x200). It had many improvements, but the clock speed was still only 4 MHz. In 1986, Sharp released the X1 turbo Z series with a 4096 color analog RGB monitor. An X1 twin, which had a PC-Engine in the cabinet, was finally released as the last machine of the X1 series in 1987. Then this series was succeeded by the X68000 series.

Sharp continues to sell desktop PC/TV combos in Japan through its Internet Aquos line, where an X1-style red color scheme is available.</systemDescription>
      <systemManufacturer>Sharp</systemManufacturer>
      <systemReleaseYear>1982</systemReleaseYear>
      <systemReleaseDate>1982</systemReleaseDate>
      <systemReleaseDateFormated>1982</systemReleaseDateFormated>
      <systemHardwareType>Computer</systemHardwareType>
      <systemCoverSize>3-4</systemCoverSize>
      <systemColor>B73538</systemColor>
      <systemColorPalette1>752421</systemColorPalette1>
      <systemColorPalette2>4A90CB</systemColorPalette2>
      <systemColorPalette3>C1C3D1</systemColorPalette3>
      <systemColorPalette4>28333D</systemColorPalette4>
   </variables>
   <language name="es_ES">
      <variables>
         <systemDescription>El X1 (エックスワン, Ekkusuwan), a veces llamado Sharp X1, es una serie de computadoras domésticas lanzadas por Sharp Corporation desde 1982 hasta 1988. Estaba basada en un procesador Z80.

A pesar de que la División de Computadoras de Sharp Corporation había lanzado la serie MZ, de repente la División de Televisión presentó una nueva serie de computadoras llamada X1. En el momento en que se lanzó el X1 original, todas las demás computadoras domésticas generalmente tenían un lenguaje BASIC en ROM. Sin embargo, el X1 no tenía un BASIC en ROM y necesitaba cargar el intérprete Hu-BASIC desde una cinta de casete. Por otro lado, este concepto permitía disponer de un área de RAM libre lo más grande posible cuando no se utilizaba BASIC. Esta política fue originalmente adoptada de la serie Sharp MZ y en Japón se les llamaba computadoras limpias. La forma del gabinete del X1 también era mucho más estilizada que la de otras computadoras de la época y se podía elegir entre varios colores de gabinete (incluido el rojo).

El monitor RGB del X1 tenía un sintonizador de televisión y la pantalla de la computadora podía superponerse sobre la señal de TV. Todas las funciones de la TV podían ser controladas desde un programa de computadora. La fuente de caracteres era completamente programable (conocida como PCG) con color de 4 bits, y fue utilizada de manera efectiva en muchos juegos. Toda la memoria VRAM estaba mapeada en el área de E/S, por lo que podía ser controlada sin necesidad de cambiar de banco de memoria. Gracias a estas características, el X1 era una máquina muy potente para el software de juegos.

Mientras el X1 luchaba por venderse, el PC-8801 (de NEC) se volvía rápidamente popular en el mercado japonés. En 1984, Sharp lanzó la serie X1 turbo con gráficos de alta resolución (640x400, mientras que el X1 original tenía 640x200). Contaba con muchas mejoras, pero la velocidad del procesador seguía siendo de solo 4 MHz. En 1986, Sharp lanzó la serie X1 turbo Z con un monitor RGB analógico de 4096 colores. Finalmente, se lanzó el X1 twin, que tenía una PC-Engine integrada en el gabinete, como el último modelo de la serie X1 en 1987. Luego, esta serie fue sucedida por la serie X68000.

Sharp continúa vendiendo computadoras de escritorio combinadas con TV en Japón a través de su línea Internet Aquos, donde aún está disponible un esquema de color rojo al estilo del X1.</systemDescription>
         <systemReleaseDateFormated>1982</systemReleaseDateFormated>
         <systemHardwareType>Computadora</systemHardwareType>
      </variables>
   </language>
</theme>