<theme>
   <variables>
      <systemName>Xbox 360</systemName>
      <systemDescription>The Xbox 360 is a home video game console developed by Microsoft. As the successor to the original Xbox, it is the second console in the Xbox series. It competed with Sony's PlayStation 3 and Nintendo's Wii as part of the seventh generation of video game consoles. It was officially unveiled on MTV on May 12, 2005, with detailed launch and game information announced later that month at the 2005 Electronic Entertainment Expo.

The Xbox 360 features an online service, Xbox Live, which was expanded from its previous iteration on the original Xbox and received regular updates during the console's lifetime. Available in free and subscription-based varieties, Xbox Live allows users to: play games online; download games (through Xbox Live Arcade) and game demos; purchase and stream music, television programs, and films through the Xbox Music and Xbox Video portals; and access third-party content services through media streaming applications. In addition to online multimedia features, it allows users to stream media from local PCs. Several peripherals have been released, including wireless controllers, expanded hard drive storage, and the Kinect motion sensing camera. The release of these additional services and peripherals helped the Xbox brand grow from gaming-only to encompassing all multimedia, turning it into a hub for living-room computing entertainment.</systemDescription>
      <systemManufacturer>Microsoft</systemManufacturer>
      <systemReleaseYear>2005</systemReleaseYear>
      <systemReleaseDate>2005-11-22</systemReleaseDate>
      <systemReleaseDateFormated>November 22, 2005</systemReleaseDateFormated>
      <systemHardwareType>Console</systemHardwareType>
      <systemCoverSize>243-340</systemCoverSize>
      <systemColor>91B61C</systemColor>
      <systemColorPalette1>92C83E</systemColorPalette1>
      <systemColorPalette2>CECECE</systemColorPalette2>
      <systemColorPalette3>2FA74D</systemColorPalette3>
      <systemColorPalette4>9D9FA2</systemColorPalette4>
   </variables>
   <language name="es_ES">
      <variables>
         <systemDescription>La Xbox 360 es una consola de videojuegos doméstica desarrollada por Microsoft. Como sucesora de la Xbox original, es la segunda consola en la serie Xbox. Compitió con la PlayStation 3 de Sony y la Wii de Nintendo como parte de la séptima generación de consolas de videojuegos. Fue oficialmente presentada en MTV el 12 de mayo de 2005, con detalles del lanzamiento y los juegos anunciados más tarde ese mes en la Expo de Entretenimiento Electrónico 2005.

La Xbox 360 cuenta con un servicio en línea, Xbox Live, que fue ampliado desde su iteración anterior en la Xbox original y recibió actualizaciones regulares durante la vida de la consola. Disponible en versiones gratuita y de suscripción, Xbox Live permite a los usuarios: jugar en línea; descargar juegos (a través de Xbox Live Arcade) y demos de juegos; comprar y transmitir música, programas de televisión y películas a través de los portales Xbox Music y Xbox Video; y acceder a servicios de contenido de terceros mediante aplicaciones de transmisión de medios. Además de las características multimedia en línea, permite a los usuarios transmitir medios desde PCs locales. Se han lanzado varios periféricos, incluidos controles inalámbricos, almacenamiento expandido en disco duro y la cámara de detección de movimiento Kinect. El lanzamiento de estos servicios y periféricos adicionales ayudó a que la marca Xbox creciera de ser solo de videojuegos a abarcar todo el multimedia, convirtiéndola en un centro de entretenimiento de computación para la sala de estar.</systemDescription>
         <systemReleaseDateFormated>22 de noviembre de 2005</systemReleaseDateFormated>
         <systemHardwareType>Consola</systemHardwareType>
      </variables>
   </language>
</theme>