<theme>
   <variables>
      <systemName>Z-machine</systemName>
      <systemDescription>The Z-machine is a virtual machine that was developed by Joel Berez and Marc Blank in 1979 and used by Infocom for its text adventure games. Infocom compiled game code to files containing Z-machine instructions (called story files or Z-code files) and could therefore port its text adventures to a new platform simply by writing a Z-machine implementation for that platform. With the large number of incompatible home computer systems in use at the time, this was an important advantage over using native code or developing a compiler for each system.</systemDescription>
      <systemManufacturer>Joel Berez &amp; Marc Blank</systemManufacturer>
      <systemReleaseYear>1979</systemReleaseYear>
      <systemReleaseDate>1979</systemReleaseDate>
      <systemReleaseDateFormated>1979</systemReleaseDateFormated>
      <systemHardwareType>Engine</systemHardwareType>
      <systemCoverSize>1-1</systemCoverSize>
      <systemColor>000000</systemColor>
      <systemColorPalette1>333333</systemColorPalette1>
      <systemColorPalette2>48DBCE</systemColorPalette2>
      <systemColorPalette3>C1C1BE</systemColorPalette3>
      <systemColorPalette4>586C6D</systemColorPalette4>
   </variables>
   <language name="es_ES">
      <variables>
         <systemDescription>La Z-machine es una máquina virtual desarrollada por Joel Berez y Marc Blank en 1979 y utilizada por Infocom para sus juegos de aventuras de texto. Infocom compiló el código del juego en archivos que contienen instrucciones de Z-machine (llamados archivos de historia o archivos Z-code) y, por lo tanto, podía portar sus aventuras de texto a una nueva plataforma simplemente escribiendo una implementación de Z-machine para esa plataforma. Con la gran cantidad de sistemas informáticos domésticos incompatibles en uso en ese momento, esto representaba una ventaja importante sobre el uso de código nativo o el desarrollo de un compilador para cada sistema.</systemDescription>
         <systemReleaseDateFormated>1979</systemReleaseDateFormated>
         <systemHardwareType>Motor</systemHardwareType>
      </variables>
   </language>
</theme>