<theme>
   <variables>
      <systemName>ZX Spectrum</systemName>
      <systemDescription>The ZX Spectrum is an 8-bit personal home computer released in the United Kingdom in 1982 by Sinclair Research Ltd. It was the follow-up to the Sinclair ZX81. The Spectrum was ultimately released as eight different models (although the models after the Spectrum 128K were technically developed and manufactured by Amstrad), ranging from the entry level model with 16 kB RAM released in 1982 to the ZX Spectrum +3 with 128 kB RAM and built in floppy disk drive. The Spectrum was among the first mainstream audience home computers in the UK, similar in significance to the Commodore 64 in the USA. The Commodore 64, BBC Microcomputer and later the Amstrad CPC range were major rivals to the Spectrum in the UK market during the early 1980s.</systemDescription>
      <systemManufacturer>Sinclair Research</systemManufacturer>
      <systemReleaseYear>1982</systemReleaseYear>
      <systemReleaseDate>1982-04-21</systemReleaseDate>
      <systemReleaseDateFormated>April 21, 1982</systemReleaseDateFormated>
      <systemHardwareType>Computer</systemHardwareType>
      <systemCoverSize>3-4</systemCoverSize>
      <systemColor>8F1B12</systemColor>
      <systemColorPalette1>CA2825</systemColorPalette1>
      <systemColorPalette2>EDBA01</systemColorPalette2>
      <systemColorPalette3>009C37</systemColorPalette3>
      <systemColorPalette4>02559C</systemColorPalette4>
   </variables>
   <language name="es_ES">
      <variables>
         <systemDescription>El ZX Spectrum es una computadora personal de 8 bits lanzada en el Reino Unido en 1982 por Sinclair Research Ltd. Fue la sucesora del Sinclair ZX81. El Spectrum se lanzó en última instancia en ocho modelos diferentes (aunque los modelos posteriores al Spectrum 128K fueron técnicamente desarrollados y fabricados por Amstrad), que van desde el modelo de entrada con 16 kB de RAM lanzado en 1982 hasta el ZX Spectrum +3 con 128 kB de RAM y unidad de disco flexible incorporada. El Spectrum fue una de las primeras computadoras domésticas dirigidas al público general en el Reino Unido, similar en importancia al Commodore 64 en los Estados Unidos. El Commodore 64, el BBC Microcomputer y más tarde la gama Amstrad CPC fueron los principales rivales del Spectrum en el mercado del Reino Unido durante los primeros años de la década de 1980.</systemDescription>
         <systemReleaseDateFormated>21 de abril de 1982</systemReleaseDateFormated>
         <systemHardwareType>Computadora</systemHardwareType>
      </variables>
   </language>
</theme>